let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "C++ was developed by _",
        answer: "Bjarne stroutstup",
        options: [
        "Thomas Kushz",
    
        "John Kemney",
        
        "Bjarne stroutstup",
        
        "James Goling"
        
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which one of the following is a keyword?",
        answer: "Switch",
        options: [
        "Size",
    
        "Key",
    
        "Jump",
    
        "Switch"
        
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 3,
        question: "which is the smallest individual unit in a program.",
        answer: "token",
        options: [
        "varible",
    
        "character",
        
        "control",
        
        "token"
        
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is a constant that contains a single character enclosed within single quotes?",
        answer: "charater",
        options: [
        "charater",
    
        "numeric",
        
        "fixed",
        
        "floating point"
        
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 5,
        question: "The modulus operator uses _ character.",
        answer: "%",
        options: [
        "+",
    
        "*",
        
        "/",
        
        "%"
        
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Every variable should be separated by _ separator.",
        answer: "comma",
        options: [
        "dot",
    
        "colon",
        
        "comma",
        
        "semicolon"
        
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 7,
        question: "auto, static, extern and register are called as _",
        answer: "storage specifier",
        options: [
        "static",
    
        "register",
        
        "auto",
        
        "storage specifier"
        
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 8,
        question: "How many storage specifies are there in a C++?",
        answer: "4",
        options: [
        "2",
    
        "3",
        
        "4",
        
        "5"
        
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Signed, unsigned, long and short are some of the ",
        answer: "modifiers",
        options: [
        "void",
    
        "data",
        
        "derived data",
        
        "modifiers"
        
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Logical AND (&&) and Logical OR (||) are _ operators.",
        answer: "logical",
        options: [
        "logical",
    
        "equality",
        
        "class member",
        
        "comma"
        
        ]
      },
  
];